Gad Dayan

5792 Parkhaven Montreal, Qc

Tel: 514-984-5792

Email: gadou86@gmail.com

Cover Letter

Being an entrepreneur and a business owner of a successful Montreal base printing shop; Instacustoms, made me acquire multiple leadership and problems solving skills. After thirteen years of growing my company, I've came to a harsh realization that it took over my life and I became less passionate about the printing field. As the famous quote said by Gertrude Stein "Money can't buy happiness." And I can positively agree to this.

Therefore, I knew it was time for a new challenge. I decided to change my career path and put all of my knowledge to test. I've always been tech savvy and wanted to be in the technology field. I was intrigued in what coding can do and build.

I than started to take online courses on Udemy and various other learning platforms. My eagerness and perseverance gave me the passion of learning more and mastering a programming language. I enrolled in Le Wagon Montreal bootcamp 2020 to help me reinforce my coding skills and eventually find a position in a tech company as a full-stack developer.

With my passion and drive for coding I am ready to dominate the programming world!



5792 Parkhaven Montreal, Qc H4w 0c2

Tel: 514-987-5792

Email: gadou86@gmail.com

Website: <u>zcodebuddy.com</u> LinkedIn: Gad Dayan

Profile

My experience with the public has allowed me to develop an ability to communicate, a good sense of responsibility and a considerable autonomy. I am a determined, enthusiastic and reliable person. I would like to participate in the achievement of team goals by joining a dynamic and technology organization.

Experience

Owner, Instacustoms – from 2010 to October 2018

Meet customers sales | Manage a team with fewer than 10 employees | Taking care of payrolls | Company sales achieved on a regular basis | Manage Website | Respond to calls and emails.

Developer, MaskaMode – from December 2018 to November 2020

Manage Website | Design banners with photoshop | Maintaining the website <u>maskamode.com</u> Adding products on a regular basis | Adding content | Track sales | Shopify Store.

Freelancer - from December 2020 - present

UX/UI design | Landing page | Websites | Web developer

Education

- Le Wagon Web-Developer Intensive Bootcamp October 2020 present.
- Self-taught programming on online learning platforms November 2018 present.

Skills

Html, Css, Javascript, Bootstrap, MySql, Ruby, Ruby on Rails, Figma, Photoshop, Illustrator, UX/UI